(Past Leonard:)Yeah, experimental physics.
(Past Sheldon:)Hmm.
(Past Leonard:)-What is that?
-Doesn't concern you.
(Past Sheldon:)You'll be going to the university
every day?
(Leonard(voice off):)-Yes.
-Do you have a vehicle?
(Past Leonard:)-A car.
-And you'd be willing to drive me?
(Past Leonard:)-Well, can't you drive?
-I can.
(Past Sheldon:)I choose not to.
(Past Leonard:)Okay, I suppose I could drive you.
-Well, what's a point in my favor, right?
-Why don't you let me do this?
(Past Leonard:)Come on, I just asked.
(Past Sheldon:)Last question.
In a post-apocalyptic world...
(Past Sheldon:)...which task would you assign
the highest priority?
(Past Sheldon:)Locating a sustainable food source,
reestablishing a functioning government...
...procreation
or preserving the knowledge of mankind?
(Past Leonard:)Uh, I'm gonna go with
preserving the knowledge.
(Past Sheldon:)That's correct.
FYI, I would've accepted
any answer other than procreating.